hellobee.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Hellobee

Effective: November 13, 2011

**HELLOBEE PRIVACY POLICY**

This website is part of the Hellobee.com service (”Hellobee”). Hellobee is offered by Busy Bee Blogs, LLC.

Hellobee exists to promote sharing and community. But when you share any information through a service like Hellobee, it’s important to remember that you are potentially sharing it with the entire world. The information you submit to Hellobee may be accessible to anyone who visits your Hellobee site (including people who are not registered Hellobee users), or through search engines, mobile devices, and a variety of other devices and services. It may also be copied and redistributed by anyone who has access to it.

We take your privacy seriously and so should you. This privacy policy discusses how personal information is collected and disclosed through Hellobee, as well as the tools available to help you control your information.

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

  * Children
  * Information Collected by Hellobee
    * Registration – Required Information
    * Profile Information
    * Information Submitted to Your Hellobee Site
    * Comments & Other Interactive Forums
    * Email Addresses of Others (Sending Emails through Hellobee)
    * Verification of Age and Parental (or Guardian) Status
    * Other Information Collected by Hellobee
  * Managing and Protecting Your Information
    * Your Hellobee Site – Profile Information
    * Your Email Address
    * Hellobee Search Results and Syndication Feeds
  * Information Sharing and Disclosure
    * Third Party Advertisers
  * Information Hellobee Retains
  * How Others Use Your Information
    * Links to Third Party Sites
    * Third Party Search Engines & Syndication Feed Readers
    * Third Party Advertisers
  * Confidentiality & Security
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Non-US Residents
  * Questions or Suggestions

**CHILDREN**

**Children under 13 are not allowed to register for Hellobee accounts.** It is Hellobee’s policy not to collect information from children under 13.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED BY HELLOBEE**

Hellobee may collect certain information from you as described below. Hellobee uses the information it collects for authentication purposes, to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to provide aggregated, anonymous reporting for Hellobee or third parties, to improve our services, and to communicate with you as part of the Hellobee service.

**Registration – Required Information**

When you register for a Hellobee account, Hellobee requires you to provide the following information:

  * _Username_ – a unique nickname or handle that acts as your primary identifier to other Hellobee users and visitors, or viewers of Hellobee material on other systems (e.g. search engines, RSS readers, cell phones, etc.). It is always publicly displayed, so please choose carefully.
  * _Password_ – required for signing into your Hellobee account. Your password provides access to all of the information in your account, so never share your password with anyone except a parent or guardian.
  * _Email Address_ – an email address is required so that Hellobee can contact you about your account. In addition, Hellobee has several features through which information may be forwarded to this email address – including messages or invitations from other Hellobee users, alerts, or logs of activity related to your account. You can control whether you receive certain of these emails by using the settings inside your Hellobee account. Your email address is never publicly displayed on Hellobee.

**Profile Information**

After you have registered for a Hellobee account, you are given the opportunity to fill out information on our profile pages. Filling out the profile pages is optional – you are not required to fill out any of the profile information. If you choose to fill out the profile information, please note that this information will be posted on your Hellobee site (See “Information Submitted to Your Hellobee Site”) and will potentially be accessible to the entire world.

**Information Submitted to Your Hellobee Site**

As a registered member of Hellobee, you get a personal profile (called a “Hellobee profile”) where you can publish an avatar, additional profile information, etc. When you “publish” information to the Hellobee site, this means you are sharing the information publicly.

**Comments & Other Interactive Forums**

Hellobee offers many ways for users to interact by posting information to each others’ Hellobee profiles or other parts of Hellobee. These features include comments on Walls, threads, and the like (collectively, “comments”).

Please be aware that you may have limited control over comments that you post to the Hellobee site.

**Email Addresses of Others (Sending Emails through Hellobee)**

For features such as inviting others to join Hellobee or participate in specific areas of the service (collectively, “invitations”), or for forwarding information published through the service, you may provide email addresses of others to Hellobee.

Hellobee stores the email addresses that you provide and uses them solely to contact the owner of the email address. For invitations, Hellobee sends one invitation email and may send multiple invitation reminders; for other email-based communications, Hellobee may send an email specific to that communication (e.g. a copy of a specific post that you are forwarding). Hellobee does not share, sell or rent these email addresses with any third parties (other than certain contractors performing work for Hellobee under confidentiality agreements – see “INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE” below).

**Verification of Parental (or Guardian) Status**

Persons under the age of 13 are not permitted to become Hellobee members and it is Hellobee’s policy not to collect any personally identifiable information from persons under 13. If you discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Hellobee account, you may alert Hellobee and request that Hellobee close the account.

**Other Information Collected by Hellobee**

_Browser Information_

Every time you visit a page on the Internet, your web browser sends specific information to the web site you are visiting. Hellobee’s servers automatically collect and store this information, including your IP address, specific type of browser software, the pages you visit at Hellobee, and information from Hellobee cookies (see below). This information is also collected by third-party tracking companies that provide traffic analytics to Hellobee.

_Cookies_

Hellobee may set and access Hellobee cookies on your computer.

Like most sites that have interactive features, Hellobee uses cookies to recognize you when you return to Hellobee and to keep track of when you are signed in (so you don’t have to re-sign in every time you visit a new page at Hellobee). Hellobee also uses cookies to target advertisements based on information provided by you (e.g. profile information suggesting age, gender, or interests), browser information (e.g. geographic location based on your IP address), or past activities on Hellobee (e.g. whether or not you’ve seen or responded to a specific advertisement already).

Some third-party advertisers may also set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

Most browsers come with the ability to restrict cookies from specific or unknown sources. Please review your browser’s documentation for more information. Please be aware, however, that many Hellobee features will not be available to you if you block the placement of our cookies on your computer.

_Error Logs_

If an error occurs in Hellobee’s systems while you are using the service, Hellobee’s servers may automatically collect and store information relating to that error, including your browser information, information from Hellobee cookies, and other information that you may have input at the time the error occurred (e.g. information you had written into any web forms). Hellobee uses this information solely to investigate the error and help prevent future errors.

**MANAGING AND PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

Unless specifically stated otherwise (e.g. on the page where you submit the information), any information that you submit to Hellobee may be accessible to the entire world.

**Your Hellobee Site – Profile Information**

Unless specifically stated otherwise (e.g. on the page where you submit the information), any information that you choose to fill out on our profile pages will be posted on your Hellobee site and will be potentially accessible to the entire world.

Filling out the profile pages is optional. You are not required to fill out any of the profile information. If you do fill out any profile information, you may also delete or edit this profile information by using the controls inside your Hellobee account.

**Your Email Address**

Hellobee requires that you provide an email address when registering for a Hellobee account. You can edit this email address by using the controls inside your Hellobee account, but it must always be an email address that belongs to you and is controlled by you.

Your email address is never publicly displayed by Hellobee.

Hellobee has several features through which information may be forwarded to your email address – including messages or invitations from other Hellobee users, alerts, or logs of activity related to your account. You can control whether you receive certain of these emails by using the settings inside your Hellobee account.

**Hellobee Search Results and Syndication Feeds**

Information that you publish publicly to your Hellobee site is indexed by Hellobee’s Search engines and made available for collection by and redistribution through other electronic services through a publicly available syndication feed (e.g. an RSS feed).

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Hellobee does not share, sell or rent any of your information, except as follows:

  * _Information that You Share_ – Any information that you submit to any public area of the Hellobee system is potentially accessible to the entire world. Please keep in mind that the moment you share your information with anyone, copies of that information can be made, stored, and shared outside of the Hellobee system. (For more information, see “MANAGING AND PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION”.)
  * _Under Confidentiality Agreements_ – Hellobee may share your information with trusted third party contractors and service providers who work on behalf of Hellobee under confidentiality agreements. Hellobee does not grant these third parties any independent right to share your information.
  * _Aggregate Information_ – From time to time, Hellobee shares aggregated, anonymous data about its users with third parties. This data does not contain personally identifiable information.
  * _Legal Proceedings_ – Hellobee may share your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights and obligations or defend against legal claims.
  * _Safety and Welfare of the Community_ – Hellobee may share your information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Hellobee’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * _Merger, Acquisition, or Change of Control_ – Hellobee may transfer your information in the event Hellobee is acquired by or merged with another company.

**Third Party Advertisers**

Hellobee displays targeted advertisements based on information including demographics or interests. Hellobee does not provide any personally identifiable information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. But advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

Please be aware that if you voluntarily provide information to a third party advertiser (e.g. you provide your email address after clicking on a targeted ad), you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you also meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

**INFORMATION HELLOBEE RETAINS**

When you delete information submitted through your Hellobee account, that information will no longer be accessible on your Hellobee site.

When you shut down your Hellobee account, or when your Hellobee membership is terminated, the posts you’ve made to the site will continue to be accessible.

When you delete information submitted through your Hellobee account, when you shut down your Hellobee site, or when your Hellobee membership is terminated, Hellobee may retain a copy of your information (including browser information) for archival purposes. Archival copies are not posted publicly on the Hellobee system; they are maintained solely so that Hellobee may recover content and restore accounts (in case of errors or system failure) or cooperate with law enforcement in order to make the Hellobee service safer.

**HOW OTHERS USE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Links to Third Party Sites**

The Hellobee site contains many links to websites operated by third parties. When you follow a link to a third party website, the information you provide to that site will be subject to the privacy policy of that site and not Hellobee’s policy. Hellobee is not responsible for the use or disclosure of any information that you provide to a third party site accessed from a link on the Hellobee site.

**Third Party Search Engines & Syndication Feed Readers**

Any information you publish publicly on Hellobee may be indexed by third party search engines (e.g. Google or Yahoo) and appear in the search results provided and controlled by those third parties. Hellobee does not control the search indexes or results of those third parties. For help with removing your information from any third party search engines, please visit the websites of those third parties.

Information you publish publicly on Hellobee is made available through a publicly available syndication feed. Your syndicated information may be collected, stored, copied, and redistributed by any third party with access to this syndication feed. Hellobee does not control the information collected or stored by any of those third parties. For help with removing your information from the systems of any of those third parties, please visit the websites of those third parties or contact them directly.

**Third Party Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Some third party advertisers may set and access their own cookies on your computer, collect your browser information when you view their advertisements, request information from you as part of a campaign or promotion appearing on Hellobee, or request information from you on a third party website that you visit by following a linked advertisement on Hellobee, etc.

Most browsers come with the ability to restrict cookies from specific or unknown sources. Please review your browser’s documentation for more information.

Any information that you provide to a third party advertiser will be subject to the privacy policy of that third party and not Hellobee’s policy. Hellobee is not responsible for the disclosure of any such information that you provide to any third party advertiser.

**Third Party Advertisers – Google**

Google is one of the third-party advertising companies we may use to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click here.

**CONFIDENTIALITY & SECURITY**

Your Hellobee account is protected by a password you create. Hellobee implements features reasonably designed to protect the security of any non-public information that is stored in our database, such as your password. We cannot, however, guaranty the security of your non-public account information. Hacking, software or hardware failure and other unauthorized access to our premises and systems may compromise the security of Hellobee members’ information.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time we may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Hellobee account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Please note that your continued use of the Hellobee service after the date of any changes to this policy (which will appear as the “Effective” date listed on the policy) will constitute your acceptance and agreement to be bound by those changes. You should visit this page on a regular basis to view any changes to this privacy policy.

**NON-US RESIDENTS**

If you are not a US resident, your use of Hellobee shall constitute consent to the transfer, storage, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in the US in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.
